[Music]
all you did was you learned to lie and
cheatting college that's all it did for
you not all I did Larry because without
that skill I would not be crushing it on
Wall Street right now
okay imagine somebody who says I can't
afford to to go to go to college but I'm
going to take 25 courses online on one
of these online for free or for a couple
hundred and then you go to an employer
and you say look I've taken all these
courses I've done well will you give me
the job if the employer says yes boom
there goes the college's pricing power
right the college can't charge 50 Grand
says get in here early because we start
the Big Max at
7:00 these are real Majors we found at
colleges okay and if you tell me you can
tell me whether it's worthwhile a ba or
if it's worthless BS all right Canadian
studies I'd say ba ba but very boring
hey America Larry Wilmore here if you
like the nightly show on Comedy Central
like us on Facebook too just don't poke
me I do not like being poked you can
Candy Crush me